compatible-astrology.com 2012-10-04

# Privacy Policy

**Compatible-Astrology.com** is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all our users. That is why we have created this privacy policy which clarifies our information gathering and disseminating practices. In this document we explain what information is gathered and how it is used.

Please read the complete Privacy Policy below and contact us if you have any questions.

**Compatible-Astrology.com** contains links to many external Web sites. The company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the external Web sites we link to.

_**Information We Gather**_

Our Web server generates temporary logs that contain the following information:

Internet address of computer being used

Web pages requested

Referring Web page

Browser used

Date and Time

The data is used by our system administrator and Web content manager to tune the Web site for its efficiency and is not ordinarily associated with specific individuals. Summary reports produced from the logs help Web publishers determine what Web browsers and pages are most popular.

_**Cookies**_

Cookies are small data files that are stored by your browser during a browsing session. They assign an anonymous random ID to your computer. In common with most websites, we may use these cookies to provide us with information about your habits and preferences. The information cookies provide is anonymous, non-personified (no names, emails or addresses) and can be used only on aggregate basis (for example, to learn how often visitors come to the site).

Most web browsers accept cookies by default, but have an option that enables you not to accept cookies, if you prefer. Also, you can delete cookies from your computer once they are stored.

_**Security of Your Personal Information**_

**Compatible-Astrology.com** limits access to private and confidential data only to those employees with a specific need to retrieve this information. We store data on multiple service systems, in controlled, secure environments.

_**E-commerce**_

**Compatible-Astrology.com** enables you to pay for products or services online with a credit card. Unless otherwise noted, these transactions are encrypted. It is the Company's policy that confidential information you enter in the transaction is used only for the purposes described in that transaction.

_**Sharing of Information**_

**Compatible-Astrology.com** does not share information with other parties without your authorization. It is against the Company's policy to release confidential information gathered through the Web, such as pages visited, or personalized preferences.

We may extend offers to users on behalf of our partners about a particular product or service that may be of interest to you, but we will never give out your name or personal information at any time without your permission. As result, although we may receive a fee from our partners for this service, we send all the offers so that your personal information is never shared with any third party.

_**Contact Information**_

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please follow the link and reply using our **[Contact Us](http://www.compatible-astrology.com/contact.html)** form.

Updated February, 2009
